Nobody else is going to tell you they're
trying to kill us. You're probably
asking, "Why do I have my Mustang parked
in the dirt patch on the side of the
road with two plastic bottles?" Joe
hates plastic. That would be because
Richmond County, Georgia has some of the
most polluted drinking water in the
United States. This website, ewg.org,
lists all the contaminants detected in
the water in all municipalities in
America. Richmond County has 14
contaminants that exceed guidelines. And
let me tell you, they excessively
exceed.
>> Bromodichloromethane, 61 times.
Chloroform, 60 times. Chromium, 4.4
times. Nitrates, 3.5x. PFHxS,
4,317
times. PFOS, 16x. PFOA, 25x. TTHMs,
203x. That's what's in your water if
you're drinking it in Richmond County.
It's coming out of the tap. It's the
only source of water you have, unless
you come to this little shack.
>> You cannot drink that stuff coming out
the tap, can you, brother?
This is a free spring in Augusta,
Georgia, off of Flowing Wells Road. My
grandma used to come get water from this
pump house, and it's still here today.
Dude, it's fresh. It's cold. It's brisk.
This is the same water that Jesus drank.
The same water the Romans drank. And
it's good for you as long as it comes
out of the earth. But nobody else is
going to tell you they're trying to kill
us. There's cancer-causing chemicals in
your water that you're drinking, you're
bathing in, you're washing your dishes
in every day. But there's still some old
things holding on. Old Flowing Wells
Spring. You know, they say water is
life, and that's true, unless you're
drinking death.